{
    "subject": "resource/Battle_of_Saigon_(1968)",
    "predicate": "property/place",
    "object": "resource/South_Vietnam",
    "human_readable": "The Battle of Saigon (1968) took place in South Vietnam.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9428324103355408,
            "question": "Was the Battle of Saigon fought in the North or South of Vietnam?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.915745198726654,
            "question": "What country was South Vietnam a part of during the Battle of Saigon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8069682121276855,
            "question": "When did the Battle of Saigon take place?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7556356191635132,
            "question": "Where did the Battle of Saigon occur?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7473238110542297,
            "question": "How did the Battle of Saigon impact the Vietnam War?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7025013566017151,
            "question": "Which conflict was the Battle of Saigon part of?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5423400402069092,
            "question": "What is another name for the Battle of Saigon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5408024191856384,
            "question": "What was a significant outcome of the Battle of Saigon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5203507542610168,
            "question": "Who were the main participants in the Battle of Saigon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2944827973842621,
            "question": "What year did the battle happen?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Battle of Saigon (1968) took place in South Vietnam.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5521_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who were the main participants in the Battle of Saigon?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5521_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was a significant outcome of the Battle of Saigon?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5521_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is another name for the Battle of Saigon?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5521_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5521_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5521_121.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5521_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5521_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5521_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5521_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5521_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5521_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5521_86.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5521_89.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents support this triple as they mention that the First Battle of Saigon, fought during the Tet Offensive of the Vietnam War, was against Saigon, the capital of South Vietnam. The context information also provides details about the Tet Offensive and the Battle of Hue, which further supports the fact that major battles took place in South Vietnam during the Vietnam War."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about the First Battle of Saigon, which occurred during the Tet Offensive of the Vietnam War and involved attacks on important locations within Saigon. This supports the statement that The Battle of Saigon (1968) took place in South Vietnam."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}